What do you think?
どうですか?
I was literally writing it.
文字文字してましたけど
緊張?
Gatchi Gachi.
ガッチガチ
It's cute.
かわいいね
That's terrible.
やばいっすね
When I think I look like someone, I feel like...
誰かに似てると思ったら、 なんか、
It's like a mixture of Fuka-chan and Moripin, right?
ふかきゃんともりぴんを混ざってるって感じじゃね?
That's right.
そういやん
It's like a mixture of the two.
2人が混ざったって感じ
Have you never been told that?
言われたことない?
You look like someone.
誰かに似てるって
sometimes?
たまに?
Who's doing it?
誰やってるの?
I have to use it lately.
最近使わなきゃ
Ah, Fuka-chan.
あ、ふかきゃん
I'm very afraid.
恐れ多い
It's Fuka-chan.
ふかきゃんなんですね
But she's much younger than Fuka-chan.
でも、ふかきゃんより全然若いね
It's not about age.
年齢じゃない
Yeah.
うん
It's literally amazing.
文字文字して、すごい
You just don't know.
じっと知らないよね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
what are you doing today?
今日は何をしますか?
Today is?
今日は?
What do you do?
何をします?
from now?
今から?
Can't you say that?
それは言えない?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしくて?
恥ずかしい?
what are you going to do?
何をする?
I want to hear it.
聞きたいなぁ
That's mean.
意地悪だよ
That's mean, yeah.
意地悪だよ、そら
I want to hear it.
聞きたいなぁ
I like saying it even though it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいながら言うのが好きなんだ
what are you going to do?
何をする?
i don't know.
知らない
This TV is so cute.
すごい可愛いね、このテレビ
Naughty things.
エッチなこと
My face is already a little red.
もう顔がちょっと赤くなってきました
So, can I say more?
じゃあ、もっと言わしちゃっていい?
Yeah.
うん
To be more specific about naughty things,
エッチなことって具体的に言うと、
What do you do?
どういうことをするんですか?
Please be specific.
具体的に答えてください
specifically?
具体的に?
What do you do?
どういうことをするの?
Can't you say it?
言えない?
It was too embarrassing.
恥ずかしすぎたよ
cute.
可愛い
That look is irresistible.
その表情たまらない
cute.
可愛い
What should I do?
どうしようって?
Just say it.
ちょっと言ってみて
Can you say it?
言える?
There too.
そこも
What do patients do?
患者の営み?
Is that also embarrassing?
それも恥ずかしいの?
How can I say that?
どうやって言えばいいんですか?
Specifically, throw something like this.
具体的に、こういうものを投げて
Hey, that's terrible.
ねえ、ひどい
That's terrible.
ひどいって
What?
何を?
Where should I put it?
どこに入れるの?
It's a bit terrible.
ちょっとひどい
I can't say it.
言えない
I'm very shy.
すごい恥ずかしがり屋なんだな
Are you saying?
言うんですか?
Those who can say it can say it.
言える人は言えるよ
I think people who can't say it will turn their heads.
言 えない人は顔をまくるかなって
You're shy, today.
恥ずかしがり屋さん、今日くん
What are you doing now?
今は何をしてる人ですか?
I'm a student now.
今は学生です
Student.
学生さん
I will get a job this year.
今年就職します
Does that mean you're a college student?
ということは、大学生?
yes.
はい
For now.
今のところ
High school students can't come.
高校生は来れないからね
Is it possible to graduate from university now?
今のところ大学、卒業はできる?
can.
できます
Have you decided to get a job?
就職決まった?
Then, even though everything is going so well, where did it end up?
そしたらなんでその順調なのに、どこに来ちゃうんですか?
Eh, that is
え、それは
...
Annual bonds are impossible.
年 債不可能なんだ
impossible?
不可能?
Yeah.
うん
Have you decided to get a job?
就職決まったんでしょ?
Don't make it in time.
それじゃ間に合わないでね
Don't cover it.
まかないでね
The system itself is strange.
システム自体おかしいな
Please give me more salary.
もっと給料出せよって
There are a lot of kids like that.
そういう子いっぱいいるじゃん
I couldn't even borrow it from my parents, so I was in trouble.
親にも借りれないし、困っちゃった
What should I do?
どうしよう
I went back once.
一回戻っちゃった
Who is your boyfriend now?
今、彼氏は?
not here.
いません
It's that college kid.
その大学児だね
When was your first experience?
初 体験はいつですか?
During my first year of school.
今校1年の時に
Did it hurt?
痛かった?
a bit.
少し
a bit?
少し?
So it felt good.
じゃあ気持ちよかったね
There might even be a sign.
サインもあるかもね
No.
ないです
There may even be a sign.
サインもあるかもしれない
It feels a little good, and it hurts a little.
少し気持ちよくて、ちょっと痛い
Pain too.
痛気も
It's like a feeling of pain.
痛気持ちっていう感じで
How many people did you work with after that?
その後は何人とやったの?
After the first time.
初めてしてから
Not everyone does it.
みんなやってませんよ
Are you doing it?
やって る?
How many people did you work with?
何人とやりましたか?
Alone?
一人?
Only that person?
その人だけ?
How long have you been together?
いつくらいまで付き合ってたの?
Until recently.
最近まで
I just said boyfriend.
今、彼氏って言ったんだ
Well, I did a lot of it when I was in high school.
じゃあ、高校の時とかいっぱいしたね
What year?
何年?
How many times did you do it?
何回くらいした?
How many times?
何回?
Why can't it be counted?
何で数えられない?
I'm not counting.
数えてないよ
It was amazing in the beginning, right?
最初の頃はすごかったでしょ?
Did you do it twice a day?
一日2回とかした?
Didn't it hurt?
痛くなかった?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It felt amazing.
すごい気持ちよかった
It already felt good after the second time.
2回目くらいからもう気持ちよかった
I thought it felt good.
気持ちいいって思った
Normally it hurts, too.
普通も痛くて、だだって
Are you going to do it already?
もうやるもんかって
Is that so?
そうなの?
That's how it happened.
そうなっちゃって
How shall we do it?
どうやっちゃう?
It starts to feel good, but from the second time onwards, you're talented.
気持ちよくなってくるんだけど、2回目からってのは才能あるね
That's it.
って
Is it talent?
才 能かな?
Have you ever said anything to him if you had been with him for a long time?
その彼とずっとやってたら、言っちゃったことある?
be?
ある?
I was kept alive.
生かされちゃったんだ
How did you survive?
どういうふうに生かされちゃった?
it is...
それは...
Can't you say it?
言えない?
If I tell you what to do, do you want to hear it?
どうしようって言ったら聞きたいの?
There are various things.
いろいろですよ
various.
いろいろ
yes.
はい
What happened to Iroiro?
い ろいろってどうされたの?
What I said.
言っちゃったこと
There is.
あるじゃん
Toys and stuff.
おもちゃとか
Oh, I brought out a toy.
あ、おもちゃ出してきたんだ
I mean, I brought it out.
出してきたっていうか
Phones, rotors, etc.
電話とかローターとかあんじゃん
What a guy.
なんてやつ
I'll go with chestnuts.
クリでは行くのね
Yeah.
うん
That's right.
ですね
Hello, hello.
もしもしもしもし
I'll go in chestnut.
クリでは行くの
What else?
あとは?
Look at Chin Chin.
チンチン見ろよ
Have you ever said that?
言ったことありますか?
it is...
それは...
Is it okay to be embarrassed?
恥 ず かしくていいの?
You said it.
言ったんだね
Did you say that?
言ったの?
I went.
行きました
hey?
ね?
Do you go every time?
毎回行くの?
Did you go there every time?
毎回行ってた?
What was your position at that time?
その時の体勢は?
Normal, okay.
正常、いいと
Did you do all the back and orbit stuff?
バック、軌道とかって全部やった?
I haven't done everything that much.
全部そんなにやってない
Haven't you done it?
やってない?
Have you ever had raw sex?
生ハメはしたこと?
do not have.
ない
Just go.
ゴーばっか
I'm scared, baby.
怖いから、赤ちゃん
Because it's scary.
怖いから
It feels better raw.
生の方が気持ちいいんだよ
Do you know?
知ってる?
Because I feel guilty too.
自分もやらしいから
It's completely different live.
生で全然違うの
If you do it.
やると
Nurnyuru.
ニュルニュルって
Rubber is rubber.
ゴムだとゴム
Sometimes you can catch fish.
釣れちゃう場合もある
I'm smiling.
ニコニコしてる
Are you still nervous?
まだ緊張してる?
I hear only naughty things.
やらしいことばっか聞くから
All sorts of strange things.
変なことばっか
I'm asking a question.
質問責めです
But it's better that way.
でもそういう方がいいじゃん
I like it.
俺が好きなのよ
Make them say naughty things.
やらしいこと言わせる
There's a problem.
問題あるよ
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
That kind of person.
そういう人
I don't dislike it.
嫌じゃない
I don't know how to apply it myself, but
塗り具合は自分で分かんないけど、
Who has ever had a hole in their butt?
お尻の穴まで誰で出来たことある?
be?
ある?
I don't know.
分かんない
There might be.
あるかも
It's going to be fluffy.
フシャフシャにいっちゃう
I chewed it, but it got wet.
チューしたけど塗れちゃう
Can't paint?
塗れない?
I don't understand.
分かりません
You can paint that.
それ塗れるね
I don't understand.
分かりません
I can paint it.
塗れちゃうな
Erotic.
エロい
It's lewd.
スケベットあるね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
There may be a finish.
仕上がりがあるかも
The finish.
仕上がりが
How tall are you?
身長いくつありますか?
166cm
It's big.
大きいね
Is it big?
大きいですか?
Make it look like cheeks?
ほっぱいに見せる?
It's small.
小さいです
S?
It's an S cup.
Sカップって
S
Please turn back.
後ろ向いてください
Please stand by my side.
そばに手をついてください
Are you going to watch Hunts?
ハンツ見ちゃう?
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
Put your butt out.
お尻付け出して
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
I don't like it when my butt is exposed.
お尻付け出して嫌だって
A shy person.
恥ずかしがい方
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
Put your butt out.
お尻付け出して
I don't like it either.
俺も嫌だ
Put one leg up on the side.
片足をそばの上にあげて
Do it.
やってて
show me.
見せて
It's impossible.
無理やねん
Don't you want to stand up?
立ってらんない?
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
We just broke up, so how many months ago was the last time we did it?
別れてばっかで、 最後、何ヶ月前くらいにやったの?
About 2 months.
2ヶ月くらい
You want to do it, right?
やりたいでしょ
Naughty.
エッチ
Because I want to put in a cinch.
シンチ入れたいから
Don't want to put it in?
入れたくない?
Come in.
入って
You put it in, right?
入れたんでしょ?
I'm sweating.
汗こいちゃってるんだよ
I'm nervous.
緊張して
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ嫌だ
I don't feel relieved.
気が済まない
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
How can I hate it?
どうしたら嫌だよ
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
Open it.
開いて
hang on.
待って
Show me well.
よく見せて
Isn't it out?
出てない?
What?
何が?
It's warm.
あったかいな
It's out.
出ちゃってる
Didn't you drop it right away?
すぐ落としなかった?
I haven't.
してない
what?
何?
Pooh.
プーって
it is?
それは?
amazing.
すごい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Don't cry.
泣いちゃダメだよ
I'm embarrassed.
恥ずかしくて
You'll be sweating less.
汗がやくなるね
hot.
熱い
I'm sweating.
汗かいちゃってる
what up?
どうした?
Do you feel like crying?
泣いちゃいそう?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Don't hide it, show it.
隠さないで見せて
why?
なんで?
Don't press it.
押さないで
Don't press it?
押さないで?
You haven't taken a bath.
お風呂入ってないんだよね
Can I smell it?
匂い嗅いでいい?
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
I haven't taken a bath.
お風呂入ってない
You also peed.
おしっこもしたでしょ
It's sweat.
汗だよ
odor.
臭い
It doesn't smell.
臭くない
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
oh
お
Shimai.
しま い
I almost cried.
泣きそうになっちゃったんだ
My boyfriend really beat me up.
相当彼氏にやられたね
what?
何?
Did you hit shit?
くそ打った?
You've been beaten.
やられたね
It's coming out.
出てきてる
I don't like it.
嫌だ
da
ダ
Me.
メ
No.
ダ メ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Get your hands on that.
そ っちに手ついて
Stretch out four stands.
4つの台張って
Keep it nearby.
そばに置いて
Leave it by your side.
そ ば に置いて
I don't like it.
嫌だ
why?
なんで?
Very tight.
すごい締める
Look.
ほ ら
It's so crispy.
ビシャビシャなんだよ
It came out.
出てきちゃった
Nothing.
なんもない
Because it's disgusting.
嫌らしいんだから
I'm starting to want to do it soon.
早 くやりたくなってきた
Can I take a bath?
お風呂入っていい?
Do you want to join?
入りたい?
You don't have to go in.
入らなくてもいい
Shall I lick it?
舐めようか
I don't like it unless I lick it.
舐めないと嫌だ
Is it okay to lick it?
舐めちゃダメ?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
何 個?
Is it no good?
ダメか
No?
ダメ?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Okay.
いいよ
You'll get angry.
怒っちゃうからね
Come in.
入 ってきて
Let's go.
行ってきましょう
Don't you like it?
嫌 だ?
嫌だ?
Can you feel my breasts?
おっぱい感じる?
Did it tickle?
くすぐった?
Yeah.
うん
Did your whole body tickle?
全身くすぐった?
It hasn't been developed yet.
まだそこが開発されてないのね
This is where it feels good.
気持ちいいところはここ
Kokoto?
ここと?
What else?
あと は?
Only here?
ここだけ?
where?
どこ?
Doesn't it feel good to have your breasts licked?
おっぱい舐められるのが気持ちよくない?
Open your ass.
お尻を開いて
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだね
My ears are ticklish.
耳はくすぐったい
My back also tickles.
背中もくすぐったい
But it tickles and it feels good.
でも、くすぐった気持ちいい
It's better not to do it because it feels ticklish.
くすぐった気持ちだからやらないであったほうがいい
Is that okay?
そういうことでいいの?
That's how it is.
そういうことで
Fusatsuke!
ふさつけ!
Be honest.
正 直 言いなさい
正直言いなさい
It's better to be honest.
正直言ったほうがいいな
Does it really feel good?
本当に気持ちいいの?
what are you doing?
あなたは何をしているの?
First, show me your pussy.
まず、 マンコ見せて
You were embarrassed because I saw it earlier too, right?
さっきも俺が見たから恥ずかしかったでしょ?
I was embarrassed because I saw it when I pulled down my pants earlier.
さっきのパンツを下ろしたとき、 見たから恥ずかしかったで
Sho?
しょ?
Make it too much.
あ まりにして
Too much.
あまりにして
Show me.
見せてほら
show me.
見 せて
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Pussy, there's a mole here.
マンコ、ここにほくろがあるんだね
Don't say it.
言わないでよ
show me.
見せて
See, see.
見る見る
Look closely.
がっつり見る
show me.
見せて
Is this hair shaved?
これ、毛は剃ってたりしてるの?
This is summer too.
これ、夏も
Is it summer too?
夏もしてるの?
Summer is also looked down upon.
夏も下に見られてるんだって
I put my pants in here to hide it.
パンツをここに入れて、 ここを隠してるんだ
Click here to the side.
ここを横にバチバチバチって
show me.
見せて
It's taking a lot of time.
よくかかってるよ
Raise your butt.
お尻を上げて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
what?
なに?
My dick is going in.
おちんち入っちゃうんだよ
Can you spread it with your own hands?
自分の手で広げられる?
Both.
両方だ
Spread it out.
広げて
Show me well.
よく見せて
Spread it out.
広げて
I'll show you.
見せてあげる
Look.
ほら
You can see it, right?
見 えるでしょ?
No.
いやだ
Look carefully.
よく見て
What's going on?
どうなってんの?
どう なってんの?
How are you doing?
よくってんの?
It's spreading.
広がってる
Is it spreading?
広がってる?
That's naughty.
やらしいね
You could be my boyfriend, right?
彼氏にいられたんでしょ?
Take a look.
ちょっと見て
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
show me.
見せて
Don't hide it.
隠さないで
Spread it out.
広げて
Show me well.
よく見せて
show me.
見せて
I want to see it.
見たいんだよ
show me.
見せて
It's coming out.
出てきてる
Look.
ほら
Wait, wait.
待って待って
It's coming out.
出てきてる
I won't go out.
出ないよ
show me.
見せて
It came out, right?
出てきたでしょ?
It came out.
出てきた
出 てきた
Is it okay now?
もう いい?
show me.
見せて
Look, that's amazing.
ほら、すごい
Too shy.
恥ずかしがりすぎる
I don't want to show it to you at all.
全然見せてくんないからね
The dog is already cool.
ワンちゃん、もうかっこいい
Push me.
押し向けて
Let's push it.
押そう
Just push it towards me.
そのまま押し向けて
Even the fourth one started to push me.
4つ目だって押し付きだして
Just say petan.
そのままペタンって
Push it up.
ペタンって押し上げて
show me.
見せて
Look, it's shining.
ほ ら、光ってる
No more?
もうダメ?
Is it too embarrassing?
恥ずかしすぎてダメ?
Are you too embarrassed to do it?
恥ずかしすぎて無理ですか?
Push it out.
押し付け出して
In a soggy place.
ぐしょぐしょのところにね
what up?
どうした?
what?
何?
I'm too embarrassed to show it.
恥ずかしくて見せらんない
Push me.
押し見せて
If you can't show it yourself, I'll show it to you.
自分で見せらんないから俺が見せる
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Look.
ほ ら
Your pussy is small, isn't it?
マンコ小っちゃいよね
That's amazing.
すごいね
My pussy is small.
マンコ小っちゃい
It's really small compared to its size.
体の割には本当に小ぶりなんだもん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Don't you like it anymore?
もう嫌だ?
I want to show you guys.
見せてみたいんだからみんな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
I could also see her butthole.
お尻の穴も見えちゃった
I don't like it.
嫌だ
When did you poop?
うんちいつしたの?
It stinks when I open it.
開けて臭いから
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Because it smells like poop.
うんちゃん臭いするから
I absolutely hate it.
絶対嫌だ
I understand, I understand.
分かった分かった
Look.
ほら
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It seems like they don't like widening it.
ひろがるの嫌らしいじゃん
You'll hate it.
嫌がっちゃうよ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I turned red.
赤くなっちゃった
It's my fault.
俺のせい
Is it my fault?
俺のせい?
Yeah.
うん
Is it my fault?
俺のせい?
The tingling of the hair is amazing.
毛のゾクゾクがすごい
terrible.
やばい
Did you turn on the switch?
スイッチ入った?
I feel like it's kind of boring.
なんかグダーってなってる
I don't like it.
嫌だ
That's an erotic girl.
エロい娘ですよそれは
why?
なんで?
Will it end alone?
ひとりで終わる?
It's a shop.
お店なんだ
I'll show you.
俺が見せてあげる
Because they don't show it to me at all.
全然見せてくれないから
I felt embarrassed.
恥ずかしくなって
Sitting on the tuna.
マグロの上に座って
good?
いい?
Dislike
嫌
is.
だ
It looks good, right?
よ く見えるでしょ?
Can you find your feet?
足つく?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Don't fall.
落ちないで
Lay your face down on me.
顔を俺に倒して
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Looks good.
よく見える
It's heavy.
重いよ
It's not heavy.
重くない
Are you okay.
大丈夫
They won't show it to me.
見せてくれないんだよ
Wait, wait.
待って待って
Are you going to make me look like this?
こんな格好させるの?
Yeah.
うん
Stop it.
やめ
Don't take it.
取れないで
It came out great.
すんごく出てきた
I have to stop.
やめなきゃ
What are you saying?
何言ってんの?
tell me.
教えて
What are you saying?
何言ってんの?
what?
何?
I'm saying it out loud.
ひちゃひちゃ言ってるんだよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
What will happen?
どうなっちゃう?
tell me.
教えて
Have you gone crazy?
おかしくなっちゃった?
Never stop
や めなき
Yeah.
ゃ
Is this the end?
こんな おしまい?
What happened when it ended?
おしまいってどうしちゃったの?
Stop it.
やめるのね
Because I said it was over.
おしまいって言ったから
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
You'll stop, right?
やめるでしょ?
It's over, right?
おしまいでしょ?
Is it over?
おしまい?
Will it end?
おしまいする?
Are you going to finish it?
おしまいするの?
It's over, right?
おしまいでしょ?
Isn't it over?
おしまいしてない?
Finish it up
おしまいして
do not have?
ない?
Too much water?
水 過ぎ?
Is it too smelly?
臭いすぎ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Then smoke it.
じゃあ吸ってよ
Isn't it funny?
おかしくね?
Yeah, that's it.
うん、おしまい
Did you say that?
言っちゃったの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
What was enough?
何が十分した?
What did enough?
何が十分したの?
What was enough?
何 が 十 分 した の?
Did you say that?
言っちゃったの?
It's mud.
泥だろじゃん
Did you raise your head?
頭上げた?
It's Oshiro-neechan.
おしろ姉ちゃんだね
Have you ever said that?
言ったことある?
do not have?
ない?
Stop it.
やめろ
やめて
scared.
怖い
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Is something wrong?
何か変?
Can I do it?
やっていい?
still.
まだ
Can I do it?
やっていい?
Can I try it?
やってみていい?
It's my first time.
初めてだよ
Get some sleep.
ちょっと寝て
Are you okay.
大丈夫
to
ト
It's Ro Toro.
ロ トロなの
scared?
怖い?
Are you scared?
怖いか
Will you do it?
やってやる?
can?
できる?
You like toys.
おもちゃ好きなんだね